McKenzie Carlton

19301 Blue Lake Loop, Bend OR 97702 • (541) 350-3863 mckenziecarlton@yahoo.com

Summary:

I am a highly-motivated and friendly non-profit administrator with nearly 3 years' experience in the education industry seeking to use my background in management, communication, and customer service to take on the role of Onboarding Specialist at Odysys. I am organized and hard working, with the willingness to go above and beyond to obtain any trainings and knowledge to further qualify me for this position.

Experience:

Inspire Early Learning Center

Assistant Director

Bend. OR

- Managing daily operations at the west side location of the largest non-profit early childhood education center in Bend by exhibiting leadership and effective problem solving skills.
- Conducting new staff orientation and training with all incoming employees. Maintaining all Oregon state required trainings for current staff members. Providing daily guidance and support whenever necessary.
- Acting as a resource for parents of students, as well as the public, by providing positive and professional customer service and maintaing open lines of communication.
- Assisting in a wide range of projects and tasks including fundraisers, hiring and other HR duties, Deschutes County annual immunization reporting, Oregon Office of Childcare compliance records, and any other assignments as needed.
- Assisting in maintaining the company website using Wix, and regularly updating other social media outlets such as Facebook and Seesaw.

Delta Gamma Sorority

Sept. 2011-2012

Nov. 2014 - present

Director of Scholarship

Eugene, OR

- Maintaining scholarship records, organizing study times.
- Implementing new methods on holding members accountable for grades.
- Updating Executive Offices regularly on scholarship status.
- Making public speeches and instructing large groups.

Education:

University of Oregon BS in General Science

2009 - 2013